你想他们有昨天的《每日新闻报》吗
Do you think they have yesterday's Daily News?
干吗
Why?
我只想看看我的星座占卜准不准
I just wanna check my horoscope, see if it was right.
天啊  菲比  别看  你背后有个男的
Oh,my God! Don't look now. Behind you there's a guy...
完全有可能让咱俩心碎欲绝  痛不欲生
...who can break our hearts and plunge us into depression.
哪呢
Where?
到妈妈这来吧
Come to mama.
他来了  冷静  淡定  淡定
He's coming. Be cool. Be cool. Be cool.
-帽子不错  -谢谢
- Nice hat. - Thanks.
咱们得做点什么  吹口哨
We should do something. Whistle.
不能吹口哨
I'm not whistling.
-来吧  吹吧  -不
- Come on, do it! - No.
吹吹吹
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
我不敢相信你居然这么干了
I can't believe you did that.
我为什么要喊"呜哇哦"啊
Why did I whoo- hoo?
难道我期望  他回过头来然后说
Was I hoping he'd turn around and say...
"我喜欢那声音  我现在就要你"
..."I love that sound. I must have you now"?
我只希望我们能帮上一点忙
I wish there was something we could do.
你好
Hello.
你好  昏迷的帅哥
Hello, coma guy.
起来  你个美女杀手  起来起来
Get up, you Girl Scout! Up,up,up!
菲比  你在干什么
Phoebe, what are you doing?
也许没人试过这个方法
Maybe nobody's tried this.
希望至少能知道他的名字
I wish we at least knew his name.
瞧他这张脸
Look at that face.
即使他在昏迷中仍一副聪明样
I mean, even sleeping, he looks smart.
我猜他是个律师
I doubt he is a lawyer.
你看到他手指节上的茧子了吗
Yeah, but did you see the dents in his knuckless?
这意味着他是个艺术家
That means he's artistic.
他是律师  但是兼职教雕塑
Okay. He's a Lawyer who teaches sculpting on the side.
而且他会跳舞
And he can dance.
他是那种静静听你讲话的人
And he's the kind of guy who, when you're talking, he's listening...
而不会是那种嘴上说"我了解"
... not saying, "I understand"...
心里却猜想着你裸体的男人
... but really wondering what you look like naked.
我希望男生都像他这样
I wish all guys could be like him.
我知道
I know.
城里难道没有适合你们的清醒男生吗
Are there no conscious men in the city for you two?
他身旁没人照顾
He doesn't have anyone.
我们觉得应该负起责任
Yeah, we-we feel kinda of responsible.
我不敢相信你会喊出"呜哇哦"
I can't believe you said"whoo-hoo."
连我都不说"呜哇哦"
I don't even say"whoo-hoo."
哦  她要出场了
Oh, she's coming up. She's coming up!
观众朋友们  稍后
Folks, when we come back
我们将会讨论她的新书《往日谊情》
we'll be talking about her new book, 'Euphoria Unbound':
以及永远都那么迷人的诺拉·泰勒·宾
the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
该让你的孩子上床睡觉了
You might wanna put the kids to bed for this one
咱们不用非得看这个
Y'know, we don't have to watch this.
Showtime  HBO和Cinemax都
Weekend At Bernie's is on
正在播《老板度假去》呢
Showtime, HBO, and Cinemax.
没门  省省吧
No way, forget it.
拜托  她是你妈妈
C'mon, she's your mom!
没错  《老板度假去》正上演
Exactly. Weekend at Bernie 's
尸体的腹股沟被打了二三十下哦
Dead guy getting hit in the groin 20, 30 times.
钱德勒  我得告诉你
Chandler, I gotta tell you,
我爱你妈妈写的书  我很喜欢读
I love your mom's books! I love her books!
坐飞机的时候我必须看她的书
I can't get on a plane without one.
她的书简直棒极了
I mean, this is so cool.
是啊  如果你在11岁大的时候
Yeah, well, you wouldn't think it was cool
你的朋友都竞相传阅
if you're eleven years old
《情妇婊子》79页时
and all your friends are
你就不会觉得棒了
passing around page 79 of "Mistress Bitch".
拜托  钱德勒  我喜欢你妈妈
C'mon, Chandler, I love your mom.
我觉得她不同凡响
I think she's a blast.
你这样说是因为她不是你妈
You can say that because she's not your mom.
拜托  她可是
Oh, please. She's the
-亲爱的  -晚上好
- Hi, sweetie. - Bona sera
那个意大利佬什么时候从罗马回来了
When did "Rigatoni" get back from Rome?
-昨晚  -真的
- Last night. - Really?
这么说他的飞机没在空中炸成火球
So, his plane didn't explode in a big ball of fire?
只是我做过的一个梦
Just a dream I had.
但  呼
But, phew!
她上场了
Hey hey hey! She's on.
诺拉·宾
Nora Bing.
再谈你的书吧
Back to the book.
你在伦敦被捕了
What is this about you being arrested in London?
到底是因为什么原因
What is that all about?
你妈被逮捕过
Your mom was arrested?
嘘  我正感到无比的骄傲
I'm busy beaming with pride.
说来有点难为情
This is kind of embarrassing...
但是有时候在和男人亲热之后
...but occasionally,after I've been intimate with a man...
她现在竟然会说难为情
Why would she say that's embarrassing?
我会非常想吃宫保鸡丁
...I just get this craving for kung pao chicken.
说得太详细了
That's too much information.
现在你正到处为新书做宣传
Alright, so now you're doing this whole book tour thing,
有什么计划吗
how is that going?
好吧  明天我将
Oh, fine. I'm leaving for
前往纽约  我不喜欢那里
New York tomorrow, which I hate.
不过我可以去看看我儿子  我爱他
But I get to see my son, who I love.
我只能通过这种方式得知情况
This is the way that I find out.
大多数妈妈都会使用电话
Most moms use the phone.
请别误会
Y'know, don't take this wrong,
我一点没看出你已为人母
I just don't see you as a mom somehow..
我不是那个意思  我没有恶意的
I don't mean that, I don't mean that bad.
没事  我是个很开明的妈妈
Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
我儿子的第一个保险套都是我买给他的
I bought my son his first condoms.
然后他就欲火焚身了
And then he burst into flames.
议会正在讨论一项新的赤字削减法案
Let's see. Congress is debating a new deficit- reduction bill.
市长打算再次提高地铁票价
The mayor wants to raise subway fares again.
今天最高气温45度
The high today was 45.
还有各种比赛正在进行
And- oh, teams played sports.
格伦怎么样了
What about GIen?
可以叫他格伦的
He could be a GIen.
不  还不够特别
Nah... not-not special enough.
阿伽门农怎么样
How about Agamemnon?
太特别了
Way too special.
我饿死了  我想吃什么呢
I'm famished. What do I want?
拜托  别又是宫保鸡丁
PIease, God, don't let it be kung pao chicken.
你看节目了  感觉如何
You watched the show. What did you think?
我觉得你应该更放开一些
I think you need to come out of your shell.
这是什么小饭店
What is this dive?
只有你才会选这种地方
Only you could've picked this place.
拜托  闭嘴  这里很有趣
Come on. Shut up. It's fun.
来  抱一个
Give me a hug.
我想我们可以喝点龙舌酒了
Well, I think we're ready for some tequila.
我知道我该喝了
I know I am.
谁想来干一杯
Who's doing shots?
-我要  -我也是
- Hit me. - I'm in.
你呢  罗斯
There you go. Ross?
我不是那种喜欢喝酒一口干的人
I'm not really a shot-drinking kind of guy.
抱歉  我们迟到了
Hi! Sorry- sorry we're late,
我们有点  你懂的  忘记时间了
we, uh, kind of just, you know, lost track of time.
但人是会变的
But a man can change.
有人想要我评价什么事情吗
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
宾太太  我得告诉您
Mrs. Bing, I have to tell you,
你写的每本书我都看过
I've read everything you've ever written.
不  我是说真的
No, I mean it!
我读《爽在午夜》时
I mean, when I read Euphoria at Midnight,
满脑子就当一个作家
all I wanted to do was become a writer.
别这么说  我能办到的大家都能办到
Oh, please, honey, listen, if I can do it, anybody can.
你只要从描写几个欧洲城市开始
You just start with half a dozen European cities...
以30个委婉语形容男性生殖器
...throw in thirty euphemisms for male genitalia,
这样  嘭  你的书写好了
...and bam! You have got yourself a book.
女士们先生们  这就是我母亲
My mother, ladies and gentlemen.
226房有留言吗
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
-你还好吧  猛男  -嗯  我还好
- You okay,slugger? - Oh,yeah. I'm fine.
你今晚怎么了
What is with you tonight?
没什么  我没事  没事
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
谢谢
Okay,thank you.
是因为那个意大利舔手男  对吧
It's the Italian hand-licker, isn't it?
不  是因为被他舔的那个人
No. It's the one he's licking.
她应该和你在一起
She's supposed to be with you.
你真行
You're good.
罗斯  听我说
Oh, Ross, listen to me.
我的书通常都能卖出上百万本
I have sold 100 million copies of my books,
知道为什么吗
and you know why?
因为封面上的辣妹露两点
The girl on the cover with her nipples showing?
不  因为我知道如何描写
No, because I know how to write men
让女人芳心暗许的男人
that women fall in love with.
相信我  保罗没有市场
Believe me, I cannot sell a Paolo.
人们不会愿意翻到第325页去看他
People will not turn 325 pages for a Paolo.
拜托  那家伙只是个二流角色
Come on. The guy's a secondary character.
最终还是会被你打败的
y'know, complication you eventually kill off.
什么时候
When?
他不是英雄
He's not a hero.
知道我们的最佳男主角是谁
You know who our hero is?
封面上露两点的猛男
The guy on the cover with his nipples showing?
不  是你
No, it's you.
-得了  -不  我说真的
-  Please. - No ,really.
拜托  你那么聪明  那么性感
Come on. You' re smart. You' re sexy.
-是嘛  -真的
- Right. - Yes, you are.
你会没事的  相信我
You are gonna be fine, believe me.
我去街上尿吧
I'll just pee in the street.
钱德勒在吗
Is Chandler here?
-在啊  -过来
- Yeah. - Come here.
那个  关于昨天晚上的事
Okay, uh, about last night,
钱德勒  你没告诉他吧
um, Chandler.. you didn't tell...
好  因为我想  没必要告诉他
Okay, 'cause I'm thinking- we don't need to tell Chandler,
只是个吻而已  对吧
I mean, it was just a kiss, right?
吻一下  没什么大不了的  对吧
One kiss? No big deal? Right?
-是啊  没什么大不了的  -好
- Right. No big deal. - Okay.
除非在疯狂世界中[漫画超人中的地方]
In bizarro world.
你坏了规矩了
You broke the code.
-什么规矩  -不能亲你朋友的妈妈
- What code? - You don't kiss your friend's mom.
姐妹还可以  漂亮的姑妈也行
Sisters are okay. Maybe a hot- looking aunt.
但是不可以是妈妈  绝对不行
But not a mom. Never a mom.
你们在外面干什么
What are you guys doing out here?
乔伊和我正在讨论
uh.. Well, Joey and I had discussed
要早起去打壁球
getting in an early morning racquetball game.
但是  很显然有人睡过头了
But, um, apparently, somebody overslept.
对啊  你也没有带球拍
Yeah, well, you don't have your racket.
不  我没带  球拍拿去换线了
No. No, I don't, because it's being restrung.
有人应该帮我准备一个的
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
是吗  但你也没有告诉我你的手柄尺寸
Yeah, well you didn't call and leave your grip size.
好吧  看来你俩耗在一起的时间太多了
Okay, you guys spend waaaay too much time together.
好吧  我是人渣  我是人渣
Okay, I'm scum, I'm scum.
罗斯  你怎么能干出这种事呢
Ross, how could you let this happen?
我也不知道  天哪  我
I don't know, God, I...
她不像是一般的妈妈  你明白吗
well, it's not like she's a regular mom, y'know?
她  她很性感
She's, she's sexy.She's....
你觉得我妈不性感吗
You don't think my mom's sexy?
不一样的性感
Well, not in the same way.
我得让你知道
I'll have you know that Gloria Tribbiani
葛罗瑞亚·崔比安尼当年也是美得不得了
was a handsome woman in her day, alright?
你觉得生七个孩子容易吗
You think it's easy giving birth to seven children?
好吧  我觉得咱们越说越离谱了
Okay, I think we're getting into a weird area here.
你们俩在外面干嘛呢
What're you guys doing out here?
反正不是打壁球
Well, not playing raquetball.
他忘了告诉我他的手柄尺寸了
He forgot to leave his grip size.
他也没有拿护目镜
He didn't get the goggles.
看来你们俩似乎有点猫腻啊
Well, sounds like you two have issues.
-再见  宝贝  -再见  甜心
- Goodbye, baby. - Ciao, bela.
他们是故意做给我看的吗
Do they wait for me to do this?
-你准备告诉他吗  -我干吗要告诉他
- So are you gonna tell him? - Why would I tell him?
如果你不说  他妈妈或许会说
How about 'cause if you don't, his mother might.
你俩干嘛呢
What are you guys doing here?
他连护裆都没有穿
Uhhhh.... he's not even wearing a jockstrap.
我刚问了什么
What did I ask?
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
没事  我只是顺路过来  我从那个
Nothing. I just thought I'd stop by, you know, after...
那个地方过来  你知道的
...that I, you know.
那么你来这里干嘛呢
So, what are you doing here?
我不是专程来这里的
I'm not really here.
只是顺路拿这些过来  顺路
Just thought I'd drop these off on the way. My way.
你经常来吗
Do you come here a lot...
自己来
...without me?
不不不
No, no, no.
那么  你觉得他现在比起早上来好点没有
So, um, do you think he's doing any better than he was this morning?
我怎会知道  我早上又没来
How would I know? I wasn't here.
真的吗  也没替他换睡衣
Really? Not even to change his pajamas?
我的天
Oh,my God.
你是我朋友  我得告诉你
You're my friend. I had to tell you.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
保罗亲了我妈妈
Paolo kissed my mom?
对  不知道你注意到没有
Yeah, um, I don't know if you noticed,
但他喝了很多酒
but he had a lot to drink,
而你知道他喝多了之后的德行
and you know how he gets when he's drun...uh
我办不到  是我
I can't do this. I did it.
是我干的  抱歉  我亲了你妈
It was me. I'm sorry. I kissed your mom.
什么
What?
瑞秋和保罗的事令我很沮丧
I was really upset about Rachel and Paolo,
我想我是喝太多龙舌酒  而诺拉
and I think I had too much tequila, and Nora- um,
妈妈太太  你的宾  又对我非常好
Mrs. Mom- your Bing- was just being nice, y'know,
不过什么事情都没有发生
and- But nothing happened,
什么都没有  你问乔伊
Nothing. Ask Joey.
-乔伊  进来了  -你知道这件事
- Joey came in - You knew about this?
你知道的  知道这个概念很值得玩味的
You know, knowledge is a tricky thing.
我一整天都跟你在一起  为啥不告诉我
I spent the entire day with you, why didn't you tell me?!
喂喂  他们被我逮到算你幸运
Hey, hey, hey, you're lucky I caught them when I did,
不然后果可不堪设想
or else who knows what woulda happened.
谢了  老兄  帮大忙了
Thanks, man. Big help.
真不敢相信  你脑子里想什么呢
I can't believe this! What the hell were you thinking?
我没有  我不是  我
I wasn't- I mean, I-
你知道吗  我所有的朋友中
Y'know, of all my friends,
没谁比你更了解我和我妈之间的纠结事
no-one knows the crap I go through with my mom more than you.
-我知道  -我无法相信你会做这种事
- I know. - I can't believe you did this.
我也是  话说
Me neither, y'know what-
我还生气你没有告诉我呢
I'm still mad at you for not telling me.
你气我什么
What are you mad at me for?
你总得让我摔个门吧
You gotta let me slam the door.
钱德勒  我又没亲她  他亲的
Chandler- I didn't kiss her, he did.
-破坏规矩就是这种下场  -乔伊
- See what happens when you break the code?  - Joey-
《被扒光的女人》  瑞秋·凯伦·格林
"A Woman Undone, by Rachel Karen Greene."
对  我想尝试一下
Yeah. Thought I'd give it a shot.
我还在写第一章
I'm still on the first chapter.
你认为他的"爱棒"从粗斜纹棉布料中
Now, do you think his 'love stick
释放了出来  怎么样
can be liberated from its denim prison'?
我想可以吧
Yeah, I'd say so.
另外  饱满的满  不是"慢"
And there's no"J" in"engorged."
嘿  瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
-好啊  -好
- Hello. - Hello.
-今晚要去医院吗  -不  你呢
- Going to the hospital tonight? - No. You?
不  你呢
No. You?
你刚问过了
You just asked me.
好吧  也许这是一个有陷阱的问题
Okay, maybe it was a trick question.
瑞秋  我们现在能开始了吗
Rachel,can we do this now?
好的  我好兴奋
Okay. I am so hot.
这是一张我父母结婚时候的照片
Now, here's a picture of my mother and father on their wedding day.
你能说我妈不迷人吗
Now you tell me she's not a knockout.
真不敢相信咱们会讨论这个问题
I can't believe we're having this conversation.
拜托  只要想象她没有怀孕的样子就好
C'mon! Just try to picture her not pregnant, that's all.
中央公园很荣幸为各位介绍菲比·布菲小姐
Central Perk is proud to present Miss Phoebe Buffay.
谢谢  嗯  好吧
Thanks, um, 'kay
第一首歌是关于我最近刚认识的一个男人
I'd like to start with a song that's about a man I recently met...
那个人  对我来说已经越来越重要了  好
...who's come to be very important to me. 'Kay.
*你无须醒来当我的男人*
*You don't have to be awake to be my man*
*只要你还有一口气我就会握住你的手*
*As long as you have brainwaves I'll be there to hold your hand*
*虽然我们相遇不久*
*Though we just met the other day*
*不过我有些话要对你说*
*There's something I have got to say*
谢谢各位  我得稍微休息一下了
Okay, thank you very much, I'm gonna take a short break.
好吧  感谢菲比小姐的演唱
Okay, that was Phoebe Buffay, everybody. Woo!
-她在搞什么  -菲比刚刚开始
- What the hell was that? - Phoebe just started
我是和乔伊讲话
Yeah, I believe I was talking to Joey,
明白吗  亲妈妈的家伙
alright there, Mother-Kisser?
亲妈妈的家伙
"Mother-kisser."
我闭嘴就是了
I'll shut up.
钱德勒  我能说几句话吗
Chandler, can I just say something?
我知道你仍在生我的气
I-I know you're still mad at me,
我只是想  那晚一共就两个人  对吧
I just wanna say that there were two people there that night. Okay?
两个嘴唇
Two sets of lips.
是哦  她发生这种事情很正常
Yes, well, I expect this from her. Okay?
她一直是我的弗洛伊德梦魇
She's always been a Freudian nightmare.
好吧  如果她经常做出这种事情
Okay, well, if she always behaves like this,
为什么你不说她呢
why don't you say something?
因为太复杂了  这太麻烦了
Because it's complicated, it's complex-
喂  亲我妈妈的人可是你啊
Hey, you kissed my mom.
我们正在排练希腊话剧
We' re rehearsing a Greek play.
真是有趣  排练完没
That's very  funny. Are we done now?
还没  你不准备跟她谈谈
No! Okay, you mean, you're not gonna talk to her,
你不准备告诉她你的感受吗
you're not gonna tell her how you feel?
不要
That would be no.
别以为你和我妈妈玩了湿吻
Look, just because you played tonsil tennis with my mom...
就自以为了解她
doesn't mean you know her. Alright?
相信我  跟她没法谈
Trust me, you can't talk to her.
是你不能  还是你不敢
Okay. "You can't"? Or you can't?
好吧  我的手指
Okay, that's my finger.
我的膝盖
That's, that's my knee.
还在排练
Still doing the play.
你把他怎么了
Alright, whadyou do with him?
-你醒了  -瞧瞧你
- You're awake. - Look at you.
感觉如何
How, how do you feel?
头有点晕  基本上还行
Uh, a little woozy, but basically okay.
你的气色好极了
Gosh, you look good.
我感觉还行
I feel good.
你们是谁
Who are you?
-对不起  -我叫菲比·布菲
- Sorry. - I'm Phoebe Buffay.
我叫莫妮卡·盖勒  我一直在照顾你
I'm Monica Geller. I've been taking care of you.
我们都在照顾你
We both have.
这个雕刻画也是你们送的
So, the Etch-a-Sketch is from you guys?
实际上是我送的
Well, actually it's just from me.
我替你做脚底按摩
I got you the foot massager.
知道是谁帮你刮胡子的吗  是我
You know who shaved you? That was me
-我念书给你听  -我唱过歌
- I read to you. - I sang.
谢了
Well,thanks.
-不客气  -没关系
- Oh,my pleasure. - You' re welcome.
我想  那就再见了
So I guess I'II see you around.
什么  就这样
What? That's it?
那就再见了
"See you around"?
-不然要我说什么  -我不知道
- Well, what do you want me to say? - I don't know.
或许
Maybe...
该说"你们真好"
..."That was nice."
"我太感动了"
" It meant something to me."
"我会打电话给你的"
" I'll call you."
-好吧  我会打的  -一点诚意都没有
- Alright. I'll call you. - I don't think you mean that.
男生都这样
This is so typical.
我们付出  付出
You know, we give and we give...
再付出
...and we give.
然后  我们得不到任何回报
And then- we just get nothing back!
突然有一天
And then one day, y'know,
你醒了  然后说"那就再见吧"
it's just, you wake up, and "See you around!"
走吧  菲比
Let's go, Phoebe.
知道吗  我们以为你与众不同
You know what? We thought you were different.
但我猜那因为你在昏迷的缘故
But I guess it was just the coma.
车在楼下等着
Car's waiting downstairs,
我上来就是想
I just wanted to drop off
给你朋友送几本我的书
these copies of my book for your friends.
需要我在里斯本帮你买什么吗
Anything you want from Lisbon?
不需要  知道你去哪就够了
No, just knowing you're gonna be there is enough.
好吧  要乖哦  我爱你
Alright, well, be good, I love you.
你亲了我最好的罗斯
You kissed my best Ross.
好像说错了  反正差不多
Or something to that effect.
好吧
O-kay.
我做了蠢事
Look, it, it was stupid.
-愚蠢至极  -愚蠢至极
- Really stupid. - Really stupid.
我也不知道是怎么发生的
And I don't even know how it happened.
抱歉  孩子  我保证不会再发生这种事
I'm sorry, honey. I promise it will never happen again.
-你感觉好点吗  -是的
- Are we okay now? - Yeah.
不  不
No. No...
男人与门之间禁忌的爱
Ah, the forbidden love of a man and his door..
他做到了  他跟她说了
He did it. He told her off,
不只是亲吻的事  所有的事都说出来了
and not just about the kiss, about everything.
开什么玩笑
You're kidding?
他说你何时才能像个妈妈样子
No, no. He said, "When are you gonna start being a mom?"
她回答说
Then she came back with:
你何时才能成长起来
"The question is,when are you gonna realize
意识到我也很性感
I have a bomb?"
等等  你确定她不是说
'Kay, wait a minute, are you sure she didn't say
你何时才能成长起来  意识到我是你妈
"When are you gonna grow up and realize I am your mom?"
-这样比较合理  -你也这样认为
- That makes more sense. - You think?
现在情况怎么样
So, what's going on now?
我不知道  我一直在这儿说给你听
I don't know. I've been standing here spelling it out for you.
我什么都听不到  等等
I don't hear anything. Wait, wait, wait.
你看见什么了
What do you see?
很难说  他们好小  而且上下颠倒
Hard to tell, they're so tiny and upside-down.
等等  等等
Wait,wait,wait.
他们走过来  他们走过去
They're walking away. They're walking away.
不  他们不走了
No, no, they' re not.
他们要过来了  快逃
They' re coming right at us. Run!
-你还好吧  孩子  -没事了
- Are you okay, kiddo? - Yeah.
很好  好好的啊
All right. You be good.
小心开车
Drive safe.
-宾太太  -盖勒先生
- Mrs. Bing. - Mr. Geller.
你当真
You mean that?
对  有何不可
Yeah, why not?
我告诉她了
So I told her.
-情况怎么样  -糟糕  糟糕
- How did it go? - Awful. Awful.
没有比这更糟糕的啦
Couldn't have gone worse.
-感觉怎样  -不错
- Well, how do you feel? - Pretty good.
我告诉她了
I told her.
瞧  看到没有
Well, see?
或许我亲你妈不是个馊主意
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea, y'know, me kissing your mom, uh?
我们不必继续往下说了
But.. we don't have to go down that road.
这只是第一章
Okay. Now this is just the first chapter...
我要大家坦白的意见
...and I want your absolute honest opinion. Okay?
在第二页中
Oh, oh, and on page two,
他的手没伸向她茁壮的双峰
he's not 'reaching for her heaving beasts'.
什么是"耐头"
What's a "niffle"?
通常在"茁壮的双峰"上可以找到
You can usually find them on the heaving beasts.
好吧  算我不会打字
Alright, alright, so I'm not a great typist.
等下  你们看到那段
Wait, did you get to the part about
他那巨大颤抖的"笔"了吗
his 'huge throbbing pens'?
当他用那东西写字的时候
Oh, yeah, you don't wanna be around
你不会想在场的
when he starts writing with those.
够了  还我
That's it. Give them back.